Objective

Being a programmer in the future by working hard and participating in activities as much aspossible. Join the club ... Take advantage of the skills and experience I already have and programming to become a really professional programmer and bring great valueto your customers



Education

ACADEMY OF CRYPTOGRAPHY TECHNIQUES

AUG-2016 - PRESENT

The Fourth Year



Work Experience

STUDY AT HOME + UNIVERSITY

JANUARY-2018 - PRESENT

Knowledge of HTML , CSS $\,$, Javascript , Boostrap , Jquery , OOP, $\,$ MySQL, $\,$ JAVA and C/C++ $\,$

- FontEnd ReactJs, Ajax , backend php and API framework Laravel

STUDY AT ACT CENTER FOR CRYPTO TECHNICAL ACADEMY

DEC 2018 - PRESENT

Framework spring mvc java, MySQl

Design a sales website using spring mvc



PROGRAMING

GUIDING

TEAMWORK



References

Link: https://congthanh97.github.io : https://congthanh5867.github.io Github: https://github.com/congthanh97

https://github.com/congthanh5867

Language: Vietnamese English



- **6** 07/02/1997
- Male
- 0345271166
- vancong1166@gmail.com
- O Hanoi, Vietnam
- i https://www.facebook.com/c ongthanh9768

INTERESTS

- Soccer
- Music
- Travelling
- Chess